As I was going up the stair
当我上楼时
I met a man who wasn't there
碰见一个原本不在那里的男人
He wasn't there again today
今天他又不在
I wish I wish he'd go away
我愿,我愿他会离开
Where did you learn that?
你从哪里听来的?
Where did you learn that poem?
那诗你从哪里听来的?
I made it up.
我编的
When I was a kid, I made it up.
我还小的时候,我编的
What else do you remember from back then?
那时候的事你还记得什么?
Don't beat around the bush, doc. Don't beat around the bush.
别旁敲侧击,大夫 别旁敲侧击
Don't beat around the bush, doc!
别旁敲侧击,大夫!
Tell me what you remember about your mother.
告诉我你对你母亲还记得多少
I remember my mom.
我记得我妈
I remember my mom was a whore.
我记得我妈是个婊子
How long would she keep you there?
她通常让你在上面待多久?
As long as she was busy.
只要她在忙
Do you understand why you're talking with me now?
你明白现在为什么和我谈话吗?
You're supposed to be good with...
你应该是擅长...
...headaches.
...治头痛
I need something more than aspirin. Know what I mean?
我需要的可不只是止痛药 你明白我的意思吗?
Do you remember the murders?
你还记得那些杀人案吗?
I remember...
我记得...
...that Columbia is the capital of South Carolina.
哥伦比亚是南卡罗莱纳的州府
Are you the person who murdered six residents...
是不是你在1998年5月10日...
...of the Lakeworth Apartments on May 10, 1998?
杀害了雷沃斯公寓的六名住户?
That's my birthday.
那是我生日
Who am I speaking to right now?
我现在在和谁说话?
What should I call you?
我该怎么称呼你?
Call me whatever you want.
随你怎么称呼
Gary?
盖里?
Gary, you awake?
盖里,你醒着吗?
Yes, Greg, as a matter of fact, I am awake.
是的,格雷格,事实上,我醒着
I'm sorry to bother you at home...
我很抱歉打搅了你...
...but there's gonna be a midnight hearing in the Rivers case.
不过午夜将对里弗斯的案子 举行一个听证会
The defense found a notebook misfiled in evidence, a diary.
辩护律师发现了错放在证物中的 一个笔记本,一本日记
They argued to the state Supremes that it was suppressed.
他们向州最高法院提出争议 说这件证物被故意隐瞒了
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
There's no media. This all happened under the radar.
没有媒体 这一切都是在雷达的监视下发生的
The prisoner transport left an hour ago from Ely.
囚车一个小时前离开了埃里
Left Ely? What do you mean? What transport?
离开埃里? 什么意思? 什么囚车?
The diary gave them an opening to argue insanity again.
日记让他们有空可钻 他们可以再次声称犯人患有精神病
They need Rivers present, so they drugged him, put him on a transport.
他们需要里弗斯到场,所以他们 给他打了麻醉针,把他放到了囚车上
They're taking this scumbag to a hearing...
他们要带这个恶棍去听证会
...the night before his execution.
就在对他执行死刑的前一个晚上
How the fuck did you let that happen?
你怎么可以让这种事情发生?
Would anyone like to play another round?
还有谁想再玩一轮吗?
Let's get another puzzle, Vanna. What do we have?
我们再来看下一个谜语,万娜 还有什么?
-"Around the House" is the category. -Buy a vowel.
提示是"家庭用品" 挑个元音
-Pick up that trip.
选那次旅行
-Buy a vowel, you idiot. -I'd like to buy a vowel. An E.
挑个元音,你这笨蛋 我想挑个元音,一个E
One E.
一个E
-All right, 350 left. -N.
好吧,还剩下350 N
-Buy a vowel. -Buy another vowel.
挑个元音 再挑个元音
-Yes! -An I.
太好了! 是一个I
-I'd like to solve. -Sure.
我想解谜了 当然
"Kibbles 'n Bits. "
"Kibbles 'n Bits" (狗食品牌)
She won't stop bleeding.
她不停地流血
-Jesus. What happened? -An accident. We had an accident.
天哪,发生什么事? 车祸,我们出车祸了
Rain and lightning is moving into Elko.
大雨和闪电正进入爱可市
Doppler Radar has picked up a severe thunderstorm with lightning...
多普勒雷达从铂辛和兰德县开始
...on its way from Pershing and Lander counties.
遇上了猛烈的暴雨
-We could get damaging winds.... -Four times 10 equals--
可能会出现有破坏性的大风 四乘以十等于...
Four times 10--
四乘以十...
Timothy, could you not do that now? We're trying to hear about the storm.
提摩西,你现在可不可以不要玩? 我们正在听暴风雨的消息
-Sure you don't want me to drive? -No.
你肯定不要我来开车? 是的
I'll get us to Anderson, then you can take over after we eat.
我先把我们开到安德逊 吃好饭你就接着开
Turn into spin.
如果车辆打滑旋转
Apply brakes with short, firm pumps.
应快速间接地紧踩刹车
Check mirror and gauge indicator and roll...
检查玻璃和仪表显示,然后...
...to a slow, smooth stop.
缓缓平稳地停下
You okay, honey? Timothy?
你还好吗,亲爱的? 提摩西?
Seat belts, seat belts, seat belts.
安全带,安全带,安全带
-It's a shoe. -What?
是只鞋 什么?
It's a shoe!
是只鞋!
For he's a jolly good fellow
因为他是个大好人
Which nobody can deny
没人可否认
Shit!
讨厌!
-Why didn't we get a better spare? -Do you know what radials cost, Alice?
我们为什么不买只好一点的备胎? 你知道子午线轮胎要多少钱吗,艾丽丝?
Honey, don't get defensive.
亲爱的,别老是辩解
Well, if the point is to put him, Timothy, into the right school...
好吧,如果关键是要把他 提摩西,放到合适的学校...
-...it's absurd to focus... -George? George?
老是说... 乔治? 乔治?
-...on replacement tires. -What can I do to help?
备用轮胎真是荒唐 我能帮什么忙吗?
Nothing. I'm fine, but...
不用,我很好,不过...
...thank you.
谢谢你
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Alice?
哦,我的天啊! 哦,我的天啊! 艾丽丝?
What have you done?
你干了什么?
Hi, Harry. Where do I begin?
你好,哈里 我该从哪里讲起?
I have walked off the set, okay?
我离开了片场,好吗?
I know they'll say that I am in breach...
我知道他们会说我违约
...but they clearly did not read my deal.
但是他们显然没看过我的合约
They had me at a Ramada--
他们让我在兰玛达...
Oh, Jesus.
哦,天哪
I think I have a spare battery in my bag.
我想我包里有备用电池
Excuse me?
对不起?
I have a spare battery in my bag up front, next to you.
我前面的包里有个备用电池 就是你旁边那个包
-Any idea which one, Miss Suzanne? -The Louis Vuitton duffel, right on top.
知道是哪个包吗,苏珊娜小姐? 那只路易威登的粗呢包,在最上面的
I don't see anything--
我什么也没看见
Just use your fucking eyes! It's in the side pocket! Just look!
用用你的眼睛! 在旁边的口袋里! 看一下!
Jesus!
天哪!
What have you done?
你干了什么?
No, fool! If you help him, you assume responsibility.
不,笨蛋! 如果你帮他,你就得承担责任
It is my responsibility. Let go of me.
这是我的责任 放开我
Alice? Alice?
艾丽丝? 艾丽丝?
What have you done?
你干了什么?
Let me take a look.
让我看看
The driver of every motor vehicle involved in any manner of accident...
任何汽车驾驶遇见了...
...originating from the operation of a vehicle shall, within 10 days....
由于车辆运转造成的事故,应在十天内...
You got a towel or something in the car?
你车里有毛巾什么的吗?
Okay. Come help me look.
好,帮我看看
--within 10 days of the accident...
在事故发生的十天内...
...if you are operating a vehicle and it should, at any time, involve--
如果你在驾驶一辆车,任何时候都应...
-Stay here. Keep her dry. -It's okay. It's okay, honey.
留在这里,别让她淋湿了 好的,好的,亲爱的
-Open the door! We need the phone. -No!
开门! 我们要用电话 不!
Sweetheart, it's okay.
亲爱的,没事的
-Give me the goddamn phone! -The phone is dead, all right?
他妈的把电话给我! 电话没电了,好吗?
You're gonna be fine. You're gonna be okay.
你会好的,你会没事的
No!
不!
-She won't stop bleeding. -Jesus. What happened?
她不停地流血 天哪,发生什么事?
There was an accident. May I please use your phone?
出了车祸,我可以用你的电话吗?
-Please use your phone? -Yeah, sure.
可以用你的电话吗? 当然
Shit. I'm not getting a line. It happens in the rain.
该死,打不出去 下雨天就是这样
The phone doesn't work.
电话打不了
St. Jude's has 24-hour emergency, 30 miles east.
圣裘德有24小时急救中心,往东三十英里
Okay.
好的
You sit here, okay?
你坐在这里,好吗?
Keep pressure on the wound. I'll be back with an ambulance.
压住伤口,我马上找救护车来
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
Sorry. It's a step down from the Ramada, but it'll have to do.
对不起,这比兰玛达档次要低 可只有这个样子
I am not staying here. Are you out of your mind?
我不要留在这里 你脑子发昏了吗?
This is my car. You work for me. Get those bags back in this car now!
这是我的车,你是为我工作的 现在把那些包放回到车里!
I understand the bleeding person has a medical condition, but so do I.
我明白那个流血的人需要治疗 可我也需要
My lung walls have depleted cilia. If I stay here, I could asphyxiate!
我的肺快要受不了了 如果我留在这里,我会窒息的
No, please, please, please, please, please, please.
不,拜,拜,拜,拜
Please!
拜!
Hey!
嘿!
Stop. Please, please.
别这样,拜,拜
Hi. I'm sorry, my car is stuck. Can I get a ride?
你好,对不起,我的车被困住了 我能搭个车吗?
Okay.
好的
You know you're going east.
你知道你在往东走
Hospital's this way.
医院在这边
It's flooded. I mean, it's a dead end.
都淹了,我是说,那是死路
Yeah, well, if you don't mind, I gotta try.
好吧,如果你不介意,我想试试
Okay, that will be $30 cash, please.
好吧,请付三十块现金
Didn't you use to be that actress?
你不就是那个演员吗?
Yes.
是的
-Wow. -Now, is that a nice room?
哇 现在,那个房间好吗?
Because though I am leaving soon, I still would prefer a nice room.
因为虽然我马上要离开 我还是希望有个好房间
Your nicest...
你最好的...
...if that is possible.
如果可能的话
Eight's very cozy.
八号房很舒适
I tried to tell you.
我早说过
Hey! Hey, stop! There's no way through.
嘿! 嘿,停停! 没有路了
There's no way through! No way through!
没有路了!
-Lou, wake up. -What?
路,醒醒 什么?
Cell phone.
手机
-Do you have a cell phone?
你有手机吗?
Who wants to know?
问这个干什么?
There's been an accident, a bad one. A lady's hurt.
出了车祸,很严重,一位女士受伤了
-We need a cell phone right now. -Dude, slow down.
我们现在就需要有个手机 伙计,慢慢来
First, we don't know who you are. Second, we don't see an accident--
首先,我们不知道你们是谁 其次,我们没看到有车祸
Listen to me, dude, I'm having a really fucked-up, wet, bad fucking day.
听我说,伙计,我今天已经糟糕透顶了 淋得落汤鸡一样
So if you have a cell phone, give it to me now!
所以如果你有手机的话,现在马上给我!
Dude, we don't have a cell phone, so could you just let go of me now?!
伙计,我们没手机, 你现在可以放开我了吗?!
I need you to give me a lift in the other direction.
我需要你送我一程,往回走
It's flooded that way too. It's worse than this.
那条路也淹了 比这还糟糕
Ginny, pop the trunk. Let them in.
吉妮,打开行李箱 让他们进来
Hey. How you doing?
嘿,你好吗?
-Phone still dead? -Yeah. Where's your Lincoln?
电话还是不行? 是,你的林肯车在哪里?
Stuck in a run-off two miles down the road. The other way's fucked too.
困在两英里外路上的积水里了 另一边也完蛋
The kids gave us a lift. The girl was stranded.
那两个孩子让我们搭了车 那女孩的车抛锚了
-Is there another way out? -Is she a hooker?
还有其它出去的路吗? 她是鸡吗?
Hey! Is there a back road?
嘿! 还有便道吗?
Where do you think the water's going? You wouldn't get 500 feet.
你以为水都流去哪里了? 你走不出五百英尺
-How's the woman? -I don't know. They're in number 4.
那女人怎么样? 我不知道,他们在四号房间
I'm sorry. We don't rent rooms by the hour.
对不起,我们这里没有钟点房
Funny. You still serving food?
有趣,你还有吃的吗?
Vending machines are around the corner. Go ahead.
自动贩卖机在拐角,去吧
Rooms are 30 bucks in advance with picture ID. You need one room or two?
出示有照证件的话每个房间预付三十块 你要一间还是两间?
Excuse me. I was talking to you. I'd appreciate it if you looked at me.
对不起,我在和你说话,希望你能看着我
Well, I don't like looking at trash.
哦,我不爱看垃圾
We're a little stuck here, George. I don't think we can get out tonight.
我们像是在这里困住了,乔治 我想我们今晚出不去了
-She just keeps shaking. -She's in shock.
她一直在抖 她吓坏了
-Let me take a look. -What?
让我看看 什么?
Did your wife pack a sewing kit?
你太太带了针线包吗?
No.
没有
Ginny, wait up.
吉妮,等等
Six.
六号
At least we got a good number.
至少数字还吉利
-Did you feel that? -Feel what?
你感觉到了吗? 感觉到什么?
Cold.
冷
Are you the manager?
你是经理?
Yeah.
是啊
I'm Officer Rhodes, Corrections. I'm transporting a prisoner here.
我是罗德警官,教养所的 我在遣送一名囚犯
The law gives you the right to refuse us service...
法律给了你权利来拒绝为我们服务
...but the roads are flooded. I could use a room.
不过路都淹了 我可以用一个房间
-It's an emergency. -You got a radio in that car?
这非常紧急 你车里有无线电吗?
-Who's this? -Limo driver, had an accident.
他是谁? 开豪华轿车的,出了车祸
I got a lady pretty banged up. I could use an ambulance.
我把一位女士撞成了重伤 我要找救护车
Four-four-two requesting medical.
442请求医疗援助
Nothing. It's been like this for the past hour.
没反应,前一个小时开始就这样了
She's losing a lot of blood. Got a first aid kit?
她流了很多血 有急救箱吗?
Band-Aids, that's it.
只有绷带,没有别的
-How about a needle and thread? -Maybe in the diner.
针线呢? 也许餐馆里有
I'll get it. Locked up. Stay dry.
我去拿,关上 保持干燥
I'll be back with your key. I'll put you in 10.
我去拿你的钥匙来 我会把你放在十号房间
-Okay, thanks. -What do you got back there?
好的,谢谢 你后面是什么?
Prison transfer.
遣送囚犯
Maybe when you get him situated, come to 4 and look at the lady.
也许等你把他安顿好 来四号房看看那位女士
-I could use a second opinion. -Yeah, sure.
我想听听你的意见 当然
Looks like you're fucked.
你好像气色不好
Shut up!
住嘴!
-I wish I had beige. -This is fine.
要是有手术用缝线就好了 这很好
Would have been better.
再好不过了
I gotta get the officer situated. Let me know if you need something.
我要安顿好那位警官 你需要什么就告诉我
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Where did you learn to do that?
你从哪里学来的?
Pretty much where you're standing.
现学现用
Hey, is the...?
嘿,那个...?
The little boy, is he all right?
那个小男孩,他好吗?
He hasn't said a word since the accident.
车祸后他一句话也没说
No, no, no. He doesn't talk much ever since the....
不,不,不,他话不多 自从....
I'm his stepfather.
我是他继父
His father....
他父亲....
Two years ago, he left.
两年前,他离开了
Little temper problem.
小小的脾气问题
Watch your step.
走路小心
The furniture's for shit.
家俱真差劲
If you're fixing to cuff him to something, the toilet's bolted down.
如果你在考虑把他铐在什么东西上的话 马桶是锁牢的
Thank you so much for your assistance.
非常感谢你的帮助
-It's a good idea. Come on. -I got stripes
好主意,来吧 我有条纹
Stripes around my shoulders And these chains
我的肩膀周围有条纹 还有这些锁链
These chains They're about to--
这些锁链 他们要...
Let's go look at that lady.
我们去看看那位女士
-You get anyone? -What?
你有人手吗? 什么?
-Did you get through? -No, not yet.
你结束了吗? 还没有
Good stitch job.
缝得不错
Pulse is shallow, but steady. Keep her comfortable.
脉搏很浅,但是很稳定 让她舒服一点
We should take turns on the radio, if that's all right.
如果没问题的话 也许我们该轮流试试无线电
No, it's not. I can manage.
没关系,我能应付
You gonna arrest me, officer?
你会逮捕我吗,警官?
What?
什么?
How'd you do that? How'd you know I was a cop?
你怎么知道的? 你怎么知道我是警察?
No shit.
别扯了
Cheetos for dinner, huh?
晚饭吃芝多司?
-That don't seem right. -You got a better idea?
好像不对劲吧 你有更好的主意吗?
I worked mess in the service. Maybe the diner's open. I could--
我在部队的食堂里做过 也许餐馆开门了,我可以...
You got change for a dollar?
你有一块钱零钱吗?
I don't know. Let me see.
我不知道,我来瞧瞧
Here you go.
给你
You got a name?
你有名字吗?
-Paris. -Paris, huh?
巴黎 巴黎,啊
I'll get it.
我来拿
Never been.
没去过
Well, you ain't going tonight.
是啊,今晚你去不了
Please.
拜
Please be strong.
请坚强些
You see, Timothy and I...
你知道,提摩西和我...
...we need you.
我们需要你
We need you so much.
我们非常需要
Lou?
路?
You need to tell them, Harry, that I can't work, I can't perform...
你需要告诉他们,哈里 我不能工作了,我不能表演了
...I can't shine living in an environment like that.
我不能生活在那样的环境里
No, it is not about the money. It's about the working conditions.
不,不是钱的问题 是工作环境
One bar.
一条
No bar.
没半条了
Two bars.
两条了
Come on. Come on.
快啊,快啊
Here we go.
好了
There you go. Come on.
好了,快啊
Goddamn desert wasteland!
这个见鬼的荒凉地方!
Oh, shit! I just had it.
哦,该死! 刚刚还有的
Holy fuck.
哦,天哪
-Jesus, Mother of God. -Who is this?
天啊,圣母玛利亚 这是谁?
The woman I was driving.
我是替她开车的
-What the hell are you doing? -There's something in there.
你到底在干什么? 里面有东西
-Use this, man. -Thanks.
用这个,伙计 谢谢
-Are you a cop? -I was.
你是警察? 过去是
-She was in Room 10? -I am.
她住十号房? 我住十号房
-Where's your guy? -Cuffed to a toilet.
你的那个家伙呢? 铐在马桶上了
Son of a bitch.
狗娘养的
That was a fucking drive.
瞧这车开的
-Gentlemen. -Your Honor.
先生们 法官大人
Ready, Sharon? Alrighty.
准备好了吗,莎朗? 好
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada, for the purposes of--
关于里弗斯的案子,为了...
Judge Taylor, sir, with due respect, we should wait till my client arrives.
泰勒法官,现在,礼貌期间 我们应该等到我的当事人到场
-He has a right to be present. -He has precious few rights.
他有权利到场 他宝贵的权利已经不多了s.
He's 24 hours from execution.
他还有24个小时就要被处决了
But to demonstrate his mental state, which is the purpose--
但是为了证明他的精神状态,这正是...
His mental state?
他的精神状态?
Do you know what time it is? You think I got time for bullshit?
你知道现在几点吗? 你认为我有时间听人瞎扯?
That the justices called me in the middle of the night to review a case...
司法部半夜打电话给我说 要覆审一个案子...
...I already sat on, that I already decided, may make you happy.
一个我已经旁听,已经做出判决的案子 也许你很高兴
But it pisses me off.
可这让我生气
When your boy gets here, do what you want, but in the name of decency...
你的人来的时候,随你怎样 不过看在礼节的份上...
...state your goddamn case!
快陈述你那该死的案子!
Yes, sir.
是,先生
Somebody get me a cup of coffee, black.
给我泡杯咖啡,要黑咖啡
All right, everybody! Listen up!
好了,各位! 听好了!
There was an incident tonight.
今晚出了一起事故
That's police talk for, "Someone's head got lopped off."
警官的话的意思就是 "有人的脑袋被砍掉了"
Larry!
拉里!
-Caroline Suzanne was murdered. -What?
卡罗莱苏珊娜被谋杀了 什么?
-Who's Caroline Suzanne? -The actress I was driving.
谁是卡罗莱苏珊娜? 我为她开车的那个女演员
And where exactly did that happen?
到底在哪里发生的?
We don't know, because we can't find the body.
我们不知道,因为我们找不到尸体
Not all of it anyway.
至少不是全尸
-What do you mean, you can't find it? -Stay calm. Everything will be all right.
你什么意思,你找不到? 保持冷静,一切都会好起来的
Officer Rhodes is outside. He was transporting a convict.
罗德警官在外面,他正遣送一名犯人
-Who escaped. -What are you--?
但犯人逃跑了 你说...?
-Hold on. -Running free!
等等 逃之夭夭了!
Will you shut the fuck up so he can talk?
你能不能闭上嘴让他讲两句?
This is my place, ho! I'll say what I please!
这是我的地方,哼! 我想说什么就说什么!
-It's safe here. -It is not safe here!
这里很安全 这里不安全!
-There's a cop here. -Yeah, two cops.
这里有警察 是,两个警察
Wait. You're a cop?
等等,你是警察?
-I was. Shut up, Larry! -It's not safe here! I'm not staying--
我过去是. 闭嘴,拉里! 这里不安全! 我不要留在这里
It's all right. It's okay.
没事的,没事的
Nothing.
没事
-Is she okay? -Ginny.
她还好吗? 吉妮
Ginny, will you...? Stop it. Don't do this right now.
吉妮,你能...? 别哭了,现在别这样
-What are you doing? -Put your arm around your girlfriend.
你在干什么? 抱着你的女朋友
-Actually, she's my wife. -Everybody just stay here.
实际上,她是我老婆 每个人都别动
-Stay in this room. -Wait! I'm not staying here if he is.
待在这个房间里 等等! 他留下我就走
-Yes, you are. -No, I'm not.
不,你要留下 不,我不要
-I'm not. -All right. Larry?
我不要 好吧,拉里?
-Come with us. -Why?
和我们一起来 为什么?
-You know the place. -Here's what I know. I'm not a cop.
你认得地方 我知道的是,我不是警察
I don't take orders from a professional slut!
我才不听一个职业妓女的命令!
-Fuck you! -Listen. Just stay here, please.
去你妈的! 听着,请一定留在这里
Keep everybody calm.
让大家都安静
He's not gonna get too far. Not in this!
他跑不远的 在这里不可能!
Rhodes!
罗德!
What are we chasing here?
我们在这里追什么?
Multiple homicide.
多起谋杀案的凶手
I'll go around this way. Meet you in back.
我往这里转转,到后面和你碰头
Is that where you live full-time? Las Vegas?
那是你长年居住的地方吗? 拉斯维加斯?
-Used to. -What's that supposed to mean?
过去是 那是什么意思?
It means I don't live there anymore.
意思就是我不再住在那里了
Maine!
梅恩!
We'll go see if we can use this one. We'll go in here.
我们去看看我们能不能用这个 我们进去
Since that wasn't a successful attempt, we'll go in here.
既然刚才的尝试不成功,我们从这里进去
I'll be right out here. It's okay. I'm gonna stand guard.
我待在外面,没事的,我来看门
Not a worry. I'll be right here. I'm not going anywhere.
别担心,我就待在这里,我哪也不去
See, his mother usually does this.
瞧,他母亲通常这么做
Hey, Ginny. So how long you two been married?
嘿,吉妮,你们两个结婚多久了?
About nine hours. It was a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
大约九个小时,事情来得有些突然
Viva Las Vegas, huh, Gin?
拉斯维加斯万岁,哈,吉妮?
-We need to leave! -I was just talking to her.
我们需要离开! 我正和她说话呢
Something's happening! I need to get out of here!
有事情要发生了! 我要离开这里!
-Ginny! Ginny! -You don't own me, Lou!
吉妮! 吉妮! 你并不拥有我,路!
I own what's inside you! Half, at least.
我拥有你身体内的东西! 至少,一半
You don't own any part of me or my baby!
你并不拥有我身体的任何一部分 或是我的孩子!
Then why did I marry you?
那我为什么娶你?
-Don't slam the goddamn door on me! -Hey! Hey!
别他妈冲着我关门! 嘿! 嘿!
You guys, just calm down!
你们,安静点吧!
We are not leaving. There is no place else to go.
我们不走 没地方可去
There's a flood outside, Ginny. Stop it! Stop it!
外面有洪水,吉妮 停下来! 停下来!
I'm not pregnant!
我没有怀孕!
What did you just say?
你刚才说什么?
I lied.
我说谎了
I'm not pregnant.
我没有怀孕
What are you talking about? I saw the test.
你在说什么? 我看过测试结果的
Why would you do that to me?
你为什么对我这么做?
Because Alison saw you at The Hawk with that fucking girl!
因为埃莉森在猎鹰 看见你和那个骚货在一起!
-Ginny, what are we, like 15? -Go away!
吉妮,我们是什么,才十五岁吗? 走开!
Goddamn!
该死的!
-Open this goddamn door, Ginny! -No!
快开门,吉妮! 不!
I haven't been to The Hawk in over a fucking year.
我有一年多没去猎鹰了
Alison is a stupid bitch-whore, who likes fucking with your head.
艾莉森是个愚蠢的贱货,她就喜欢耍你
Open the damn door, Ginny.
快开门,吉妮
-Open the fucking door! -Not until you calm down!
开门! 等你先冷静下来!
I'm calm! I am very fucking calm!
我很冷静! 我他妈太冷静了!
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
Lou?
路?
Ginny, open this damn door! Open the door!
吉妮,给我开门! 开门!
-Open the door! -Stop it, stop it!
住手,住手!
Ginny, damn it, open the door! Ginny, Ginny, Ginny!
吉妮,妈的,开门! 吉妮,吉妮,吉妮!
Lou, please stop!
路,请住手!
Lou?
路?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
哦,我的天啊! 哦,我的天啊!
Help me! Somebody help me!
救我! 谁来救救我!
Help me!
救救我!
Is he in there? Is he in there?
他在里面吗? 他在里面吗?
Ginny, are you okay? What happened? What happened?
吉妮,你没事吧? 发生什么了? 发生什么了?
-Oh, shit. -Jesus Christ.
哦,该死的 天啊
Lou? Lou?
路? 路?
What's going on?
怎么了?
What the hell?
究竟怎么了?
Oh, shit!
哦,该死!
Come here!
过来!
They caught him. They caught him.
他们抓住他了,他们抓住他了
Why are we keeping him in here?
我们为什么让他留在这里面?
-Where would you prefer, Larry? -I don't know.
那你说该让他去哪里,拉里? 我不知道
I told you to stay in 3, didn't I? Did I tell you that?
我早让你留在三号房间,不是吗? 我有没有说过?
They got in a fight! I tried to get them to go back inside!
他们吵起来了! 我是想让他们都进来!
Should we try the radio again?
我们要不要再试试无线电?
Larry, just stay here and watch him.
拉里,你只管留在这里看着他
-Go back and look after Ginny. -Where are you going?
回去照顾吉妮 你去哪里?
Just do it, please.
只管去做,好吗?
Ed?
爱德华?
I don't know if I'm comfortable with guard duty, per se.
我不知道我是不是真喜欢看门
He's unconscious, Larry. He's tied to a post.
他失去知觉了,拉里,他被绑在柱子了
Timothy.
提摩西
Alice? Oh, my God. Alice?
艾丽丝? 哦,我的天啊,艾丽丝?
I don't remember anything.
我什么也不记得了
We had an accident.
我们出了场车祸
George? Can you keep an eye on Ginny for a minute?
乔治? 你能照看吉妮一会儿吗?
She's awake now. I have to get some aspirin to help her.
她现在醒了,我得去帮她拿药
Darling, I gotta go get something out of my room.
亲爱的,我要去我的房间取点东西
-Shit! -What's wrong, buddy?
该死! 怎么了,兄弟?
What do you got in the fridge?
你冰箱里有什么?
-You shut up. -What's in there?
你住嘴 里面有什么?
-What do you got in there? -Shut up.
住嘴
What is it, huh?
是什么,啊?
-You can tell me.
你可以告诉我
I'm good at keeping secrets. I got a whopper myself.
我保密功夫是一流的 我自己就撒了个天大谎言
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
Motherfucker!
混帐!
-What are you doing out here? -Getting shit that's mine.
我在问你呢,你在这里干嘛? 拿我的东西!
What are you doing? What, I don't get to ask a question?
那你来这干嘛? 怎么,我就不准发问吗?
I'm taking photos. There's been two murders. Before all the evidence--
我在拍照,已经两起命案了 免得所有证据...
That's not an answer. You're a limo driver. What are you doing?
那不算回答,你是个礼车司机 你到底在做什么?
Looking to win some "beyond the call of duty," limo-driver merit badge?
企图赢得某个"勤务外一章" 礼车司机荣获徽章吗? 不是!
You're not on the job anymore. You don't need to be a hero.
你现在没有服勤,不必充当英雄
There's a real, live, active-duty cop outside--
外头有个真正活生生的现任条子
The one who's managed to lose a convicted killer?
那个打算放走现行犯凶手的人?
You're a complicated cat, Edward.
你真让人摸不透,爱德华
No. Not really.
不,不见得
I think so.
我认为是
What month were you born?
你几月份出生的?
-May. -Taurus.
五月 金牛座
Same as me.
跟我一样
-Where were you a cop? -Los Angeles.
你以前在哪当警察? 洛杉矶
Were you fired or did you quit?
你是被炒了还是自己辞职的?
I took medical leave.
我请病假
It was making me sick.
我觉得不舒服
I burned out, I guess. Wasn't up for it.
我猜我精疲力尽了,无法出勤
One day I got a call...
有一天我接到一通电话...
...for a jumper.
有个要跳楼的人
A young Mexican girl.
一个年轻的墨西哥女孩
Pregnant, infected with AIDS, totally strung-out.
怀了孕,且感染了爱滋 情绪完全陷入激动状态
She was truly one of the doomed.
她真的是个很悲惨的人
I asked her to come in off the ledge and into my arms.
我要她先从栏杆上下来,到我这边来
She asked me why she should bother living.
她问我活着还有什么用
What did you say?
你怎么回答?
I was trained to tell her lots of things.
我受过训练该告诉他许许多多事情
Her dreams, all the people who'd miss her.
她的梦想啊,所有想念她的人啊
But for a second, I hesitated.
但我有犹豫了一下
And she saw it.
被她看到了
Within that second, I couldn't think of one optimistic thing to say to her.
一时之间,我想不到任何乐观的事 来开导她
So she spread her arms and jumped.
所以她张开双臂跳了下去
I started getting headaches...
从此我开始不断头痛...
...and eventually started blacking out.
到最后开始产生短暂性晕厥
So I filed for medical.
所以我才服用药物
What?
什么?
What is it?
什么东西?
Rhodes!
罗德!
-It's worse. Nothing but static! -Where's that key from the actress?
更惨了,完全收不到讯号! 女演员身上的钥匙呢?
This was on the kid.
这是那孩子身上的
-What is it, some kind of countdown? -Larry!
怎么了,某种倒数吗? 拉里!
What the fuck is he doing? Larry, come over here!
他究竟在搞什么? 拉里,过来这里!
Come over here, man. What are you doing? Come over here.
过来这里,老兄 你在干什么? 过来这里
-What are you doing? -I just went to get something.
你在干嘛? 我只是去拿点东西
We told you to watch the guy. What are you doing in your office?
我们吩咐过你在此看好这家伙 你在你办公室里头做什么?
I just went to get something.
我只是去拿点东西
How many sets of keys are there to this place? Look at me. How many?
这地方有几副钥匙? 拉里,看着我,有几副?
-Two and a master set. -Oh, my fucking God!
两副和一副主钥匙 哦,真他妈的该死!
Larry, you mother--! You son of a--! Get the fuck in here! Get in here!
拉里,你他妈的...! 你这婊养的...! 他妈的给我进来! 进来!
Why did you kill him? Why did you kill my con?
你干嘛杀了他? 你干嘛杀了我的犯人?
Holy shit! Who did that? Jesus Christ, I didn't do that!
真他妈的! 谁干的? 天哪,不是我干的!
Bullshit! You're lying!
胡说! 你骗人!
-It's your bat sticking out of his throat! -I know, but I didn't do it!
插进他喉咙的是你的球棒! 我晓得,但不是我干的啦!
Check the doors!
检查各扇门!
-I didn't do it! -Look at him!
不是我干的! 看着他!
-Why'd you kill him? -Why were you outside?
你为何杀了他? 你为何在外面?
-Why'd you leave him? -I was scared.
你为何丢下他不管? 我害怕
-What were you scared of? -You wouldn't understand.
你怕些什么? 我想你们不会明白的
Try me.
说来听听
-Why'd you kill my con? -I didn't!
你干嘛杀了我的犯人? 我没有杀他啦!
I don't know how-- I went to my office, that's all!
我不知道怎么... 我只是回我办公室一下而已!
-Why'd you leave him? -This your key? Number 8?
你为何丢下他不管? 这是你的钥匙? 八号钥匙?
Ten, nine, eight, huh? This is your key!
十、九、八啊? 这是你的钥匙!
You can't say that! Those aren't my keys!
你不能那样子污赖我! 那些不是我的钥匙!
That's like leading the witness or something. Look.
那样像是在引导证人或什么的,听着
These are my keys, okay? These are my keys. You see?
这些才是我的钥匙,好吗? 这些才是我的钥匙,明白吗?
You got a Gucci wallet? It's the actress's.
你有Gucci皮夹? 这是女演员的
Yes, I took her wallet. Afterwards. After she died!
好,没错,我是拿了她的皮夹 在...在她死了之后才拿的!
Afterwards, all right? I didn't kill her. And I didn't kill him.
是之后,好吗? 我没有杀她 我也没有杀他
-Let her go, Larry. -Get back! You won't pin this on me.
放开她,拉里 退后! 你不能把这事赖到我头上
-Timothy? -Get him out of here!
提摩西? 叫他出去!
-Put it down. -I didn't hurt anybody. No one!
把刀子放下 我没有伤害任何人,一个也没!
But I don't like cheap fucking whores! If you take one more step--
但我不喜欢该死的廉价妓女 要是你们在往前一步的话...
Fuck!
干!
Get it off!
快弄走!
Shit!
妈的!
Come on, you little bitch. Please fucking start.
快点,你这小贱货,求你他妈的发动吧
-Goddamn it! -Hey!
该死! 嘿!
Larry, stop!
拉里,停车!
What is going on?
怎么回事?
-Larry! -Get out of my way, I didn't do shit!
拉里! 让开,我什么也没干!
Timothy! Timothy!
提摩西! 提摩西!
An insanity plea was refused by the court...
以精神异常来抗辩法院是不受理的...
...despite the fact that my client is a certifiable Axis IV dissociative.
先不管我的当事人被验为 解离性人格分裂与否
To this day, he remains unaware of the crimes for which he was convicted.
直到今天,他依旧浑然不知自己犯了何罪
In 1986, the Supreme Court ruled decisively that states cannot execute...
于1986年,最高法院坚决裁定 州府不能对...
...a person who does not understand why he's being put to death.
不知道自己为何被处死刑的人行刑
He signed a confession.
他签了招供状
-He didn't just sign it, he dictated it. -Thirdly...
他不只签了,还亲口笔述 第三点...
...Malcolm's diaries found misfiled in state evidence.
官方证物里找到了归档错误的 马尔科姆的日记
Your Honor, this notebook contains entries made just before the murders.
庭上,这笔记本包含了命案发生前 的记载事项
Important to note are the spectacular changes in handwriting style...
重要一提的是戏剧性变化的笔迹...
...tone, point of view.
...语气、观念
What you are looking at are the private thoughts of several different people.
你现在所看的是好几个不同人的私人看法
With permission, Dr. Mallick will elaborate.
如庭上允许,马里克医生会作详尽解说
Thank you.
谢谢
Your Honor, there is no universally efficacious treatment...
庭上,通常没有有效疗法...
...for Dissociative Identity Disorder.
来治疗这种解离性人格症状
In theory, one attempts to move the patient towards integration.
就理论上,应该要移送病人转往整合治疗
-A folding of their fractured psyche. -Your Honor?
一种精神分裂的症状产生 庭上?
He's here.
他来了
No! What you saw was an accident!
不! 你们看到的纯属意外!
He ran out in front of me! I'm not a murderer!
他冲到我面前来! 我不是凶手!
There's a dead body in your freezer, Larry.
你的冷冻库里头有具死尸呢,拉里
-I didn't kill him. I found him like that. -Stop it!
我没有杀他,我发现他的时候他就那样了 住口!
Listen! Listen! I was in Vegas last month and I lost everything, okay?
听着! 听着! 我上个月去赌城 全都输光了,好吗?
Everything!
一切!
I drove west. I didn't know where to go, but I was running on empty...
我往西方开车,不知该开往何处去 但我车子快没油了...
...so I pulled in here at this place.
所以才停进这个地方
And there was no one at the station, so I came over to the office...
当时加油站没人 所以我来到这个办公室...
...and I walked in.
走了进来
And there, sitting at that desk right there, was the manager...
那边,经理就坐在桌子那边...
...facedown in a Banquet Potpie. Dead!
...脸朝下压在肉饼里 死了!
-Heart attack or something. -Banquet Potpie!
心脏病发作或怎样了 去它的肉饼!
He'd been sitting there for God knows how long.
天晓得他一直倒在那里有多久了
All of a sudden, this auto-parts salesman pulls up, looking for a room.
突然间,这个汽车销售员停了进来 想要个房间
I didn't have a fucking dime...
我连他妈的一分钱也没有...
...so I took his 30 and gave him one.
所以我拿了他三十块钱,并找给他一块
I just took the key from the wall and gave him a room.
我就从墙上取下钥匙给了他一个房间
Maybe that was wrong, but I was broke, and that's what I did.
也许那样是错了,不过我当时身无分文 我就做了那样子而已
Then I came back in here...
后来我回到这里头...
...and I moved Larry's body-- His name was Larry too.
搬动拉里的尸体... 他也叫拉里
I put him in the freezer.
把他放进冷冻库里
I wasn't trying to hide him. It was hot out.
我不是打算藏起他,是外头气候闷热
I thought it was the best place for him till his family or someone came along.
我想那是安置他最合适的地方 等到他的家人或某个人来
Only no one did...
结果却没半个人来...
...except more guests.
...除了多几个客人以外
So I checked them in too.
所以我也查看了一下他们
And they all seemed happy...
他们似乎都很快乐...
...so I just stayed.
所以我就留下来了
Cry me a river. This is a total crock of shit!
哭哭啼啼的,完全是一派胡言!
-No, it's not! -Admit it, you killed him!
不,不是的! 承认吧,是你杀了他!
Just like you killed my con. Just like you killed her husband.
就像你杀了我的犯人 就像你杀了她老公一样
Just like you killed his actress. Just admit it.
就像你杀了他的女演员 承认吧
-Say it, "I killed them." -Stop it! He can't take any more!
说啊,"是我杀了他们" 住口! 他受不了了!
Everything is okay now. Everything is fine. We got the guy. It's fine.
现在一切没事了,都没事了 我们逮到这家伙,没事了
-I don't know what we got. -What?
我不知道我们逮到什么 什么?
We thought we got the guy two hours ago, then--
我们以为我们两小时前抓到这家伙 之后...
You believe this shit? It's him! It's this guy!
你相信这狗屎话? 是他! 是这家伙!
He had a knife to your neck, remember?
是他拿刀子抵着你的脖子,还记得吧?
His story's so unbelievable, I think it just might be true.
他的说法太匪夷所思了 我觉得或许是真的也说不定
She's got a point.
她说到重点了
You guys are crazy.
你们都疯了
Maybe it's the burial ground.
也许是坟场
What?
什么?
Read the brochure in there. It's all around us.
看看里头的小册子,这一带都是
A hundred years ago, the government moved these Indians here.
一百年前,政府将这些印第安人迁到此处
They all died because there was no water.
他们全因缺水而死
Now they're coming back to life like sea monkeys, huh?
现在他们像海猴一样复活了吗?
Come on. Give me a break, sweetheart.
拜,饶了我吧,甜心
-Just take it easy, Rhodes. -You know, you take it easy!
放松点,罗德 你知道,放松点!
You've tried to run this show all night. Giving orders, pointing fingers!
你打算搞个一整晚 不断指挥命令,呼来唤去吗?!
You blamed my con for everything, and he ends up dead.
你全怪罪到我的犯人头上 结果他死了
I'm telling you, it's him! We all saw him run down George.
我告诉你,就是他! 我们全看见他撞死了乔治
Your actress's wallet is right there. She's dead, there's the wallet.
你的女演员的皮夹就在那里 她死了,皮夹在他那里
-What more do you want? -Stop it! Please shut up!
不然你还想怎样? 住口! 拜闭嘴!
All right. You want a plan? Here's the plan, okay?
好了,你要计划吗? 这就是计划,好吗
No one's gonna move. We'll stay here, like this, in this room until dawn.
谁都不许走,我们全像这样子留在这里 在这房间里待到天亮
No one leaves, no one moves.
谁都不准离开,不准走动
And if he tries anything, I'm gonna shoot him!
如果他敢轻举妄动,我就毙了他!
And if something out there comes in here, I'll shoot it!
如果外头有何风吹草动的话 我会开枪!
And if anyone of us tries anything, I'll shoot them!
如果我们谁敢轻举妄动,我就枪杀了谁
-We get it. -Good!
我们明白 很好!
Timmy? Timmy?
提米? 提米?
-You need to stay in here with us. -It's all right.
你必须和我们待在这里头 没关系
Remember that movie where the 10 strangers went to an island...
记得十名陌生人到一座岛上那部电影吗?
...and then they all died one by one...
后来他们陆陆续续都死了...
...and then it turned out they weren't strangers, they all had a connection?
然后他们便不再是陌生人了 他们之间有着共通点
They all messed with the wrong guy, and he was getting revenge.
他们全惹错了人,对方在进行复仇
Shut up!
闭嘴!
I'm just saying maybe there's a connection between all of us.
我只是在说也许我们之间 有着某种共通点
Like what?
譬如说呢?
-We're all in Nevada. -Shut up!
我们全在内华达州 闭嘴!
Where were you going with your con when you pulled in here?
你停进这里时,你和你的犯人要往哪里?
Carson City. Okay?
卡森市,好吗?
I was going home to Florida. Where were you going?
我正要回佛罗里达的家里 你要去哪?
I was taking the actress to L.A.
我带这位女演员去洛
I was born in Florida.
我在佛罗里达出生
Since you been in that chair, no one's died, so shut up!
你要是一直在那张椅子上 就不会有人死,所以闭嘴!
No one's died since we've all been here!
我们全都在这里就不会有人死了
-Hey, sweetie, sit down. -Where in Florida, Larry?
嘿,甜心,坐下 拉里,佛罗里达的哪里?
-Where in Florida? -Friends now, huh? Great.
佛罗里达的哪里? 现在成了朋友是吗? 好极了
-Polk County. -That's where I was born.
波克郡 我在那里出生的
-Which town? -Mulberry.
哪个镇? 桑葚镇
-Frostproof. -No wonder you left.
防霜镇 难怪你要离开
There's a town called Frostproof?
有叫做防霜的镇吗?
They grow oranges. The name doubles as a slogan.
生产橘子,防霜防霜只是个口号
I danced hallelujah the day I left Polk. Why would you wanna go back?
离开波克镇那天我可是手舞足蹈 为何你想回去?
I found a grove for sale on the Internet.
我在网路上发现有座林子要出售
Nine acres, 1200 trees. Limes and oranges.
九亩地,一千两百棵树木,有莱姆和橘子
According to the realtor, the soil needs a few tills, phosphorous...
根据不动产业者说法 土壤需要一点耕种和磷肥...
...lanes need reading, but it's real good land.
通道需要整理一下,但它的确是片好地
What?
怎么?
It sounds nice.
听来不错
Ed?
爱德华?
She's dead.
她死了
Get him out of here.
带他出去
Come on. Come on, sweetie.
来吧! 快点,小乖乖
Look at this.
看看这个
-Where'd you get that? -Right here.
你从哪拿到的? 就在这里
This doesn't make any sense. She died from an accident.
这没道理,她死于意外的啊
George was an accident, if you believe Larry.
如果你相信拉里,那乔治也算是意外
Where is seven?
七号在哪?
Back it up!
倒车!
-See, I told you it wasn't me! -That's not possible.
看吧,我早说过不是我! 不可能
I was standing right there. I saw what happened. We all saw what happened.
我一直站在那里,我看到事情经过 我们全看到事情发生的经过
He ran out. Nobody could have known he was gonna do that.
他冲了出来,谁也料想不到他会那样做
No one human.
没有人类
We're back to that again? It's the spirits, huh?
我们再回那房子吗? 是鬼魂吧?
Maybe it's the ghost of the guy that Larry put in the freezer.
也许是拉里放进冷冻库那家伙的鬼魂
Somebody untie me. Goddamn it!
谁来解开我啊! 可恶!
You know it wasn't me. Come on.
你知道不是我,快啦
-Listen. -We gotta get out--
听着 我们得离开...
Take her car and get out. You, her and the kid.
开她的车子离开,你、她和这孩子
There's nowhere to go.
没地方好去
-How much gas do you have? -Half a tank.
还剩多少汽油? 油箱一半
You can drive till dawn on that. Look at me.
够你一直开到天亮了,看着我
When you get to where it's flooded, go the other way.
等你抵达涨洪那里时,走别条路
I don't know if I can.
我不知道办不办的到
Get the kid and go. Right now. Come on.
带着孩子走吧,马上,快点
Timmy.
提米
Timmy, come on. Let's go. Get up.
提米,来吧,我们走,起来
What's going on?
怎么了?
-They can't leave! -This way.
他们不能离开! 这边
We'll see you when the storm breaks.
等暴风雨过后再见了
Hey! Hey! They can't leave! Where are they going? Get back here!
嘿! 嘿! 他们不能离开! 他们要去哪? 回来!
Go, go, go! They're leaving.
走,走,走! 他们要走了
-They're not leaving. -Go!
他们不能离开 走!
You can't let suspects leave after four people have been killed!
在四人惨遭杀害后,你不能让嫌犯离开!
-You really think they're suspects? -They're not leaving!
你真以为他们是嫌犯? 他们不能离开!
Shit.
妈的
Ginny!
吉妮!
Extinguishers. Larry, you got a fire extinguisher?
灭火器 拉里,你有灭火器吗?
-Fire extinguisher! Where? -Back there!
灭火器! 在哪? 在后面!
Nobody in there.
里面没人
Maybe it got so hot, they got cremated.
也许温度太高,他们被火化了
There'd be something left.
总会有烧剩什么的
You did this.
你干的
You did this! You told them to get into the car!
是你干的! 是你叫他们上车的!
Are you happy?
你高兴了吧?
Where is he?
他在哪里?
Nothing.
空空如也
I give up!
我投降!
What the hell do you want?
我投降! 你到底想怎样?
What do you want, you sick bastard? What the fuck do you want from us?
你想怎样,你这死变态? 你究竟想对我们怎样?
I am turning 30 next week and I just want to go home...
下周我就满三十岁了,我只想回家...
...and grow oranges!
种橘子!
It's your birthday next week?
下周是你的生日?
It's my birthday next week. The 10th.
下周是我的生日,十号
Me too.
我也是
Yeah.
对
George York, May 10.
乔治约克,五月十号
Alice York, May 10.
艾丽丝约克,五月十号
Caroline Suzanne, May 10.
卡罗莱苏珊娜,五月十号
Ginny and Lou Isiana, May 10.
吉妮和路伊西安纳,五月十号
Me, Larry Washington, May fucking 10.
我,拉里华盛顿,该死的五月十号
What are the odds? Must be 10 trillion-to-one.
这种机率有多少? 肯定才十兆分之一
What is it?
怎么样?
-Where's the fuse box, Larry? -Other side of the building.
保险丝盒在哪,拉里? 在这栋房子另一头
Ginny and Lou Isiana.
吉妮和路伊西安纳
Virginia and Louisiana.
维吉尼亚州和路易斯安纳州
Caroline, Carolina.
卡罗莱,卡萝莱纳州
Paris Nevada.
巴黎,内华达州
George York.
乔治,纽约州
Larry Washington.
拉里,华盛顿州
Rhodes, Rhode Island.
罗德,罗德岛
Ed Dakota.
爱德华,达科塔州
When I was going up the stairs I met a man who wasn't there
当我上楼时,我碰到一个 原本不在那里的男人
He wasn't there again today
今天他还是不在那里
I wish I wish he'd go away
我希望...我希望他离开了
Who is this?
这是谁?
Who am I speaking to right now?
我现在跟谁在说话?
Where did you learn that poem?
你在哪学到那首诗的?
Who am I speaking to? Look at me.
我在跟谁说话? 看着我
Who am I speaking to right now?
我现在跟谁在说话?
Doc?
医生?
-Edward? -What's happening?
爱德华? 怎么了?
-Please be quiet. -He can hear what we're saying?
请安静 他会听到我们在说的话??
Of course I can hear what you're fucking saying.
我当然听的到你们他妈的在说什么
Edward, you missed your last appointment. Where have you been?
爱德华,你上回约好的时间没来 你到哪里去了呢?
-Did I black out again? -Try and think back.
我又晕厥了吗? 试着回想一下
Where have you been?
你到哪里去了呢?
All right. I was driving this actress...
好了 我当时开车载着这位女演员...
...and we got stuck at the motel. There was a storm.
我们全困在这间汽车旅馆 来了个暴风雨
We couldn't get out because of the storm.
因为暴风雨的缘故我们无法离开
What happened at the motel?
汽车旅馆发生了什么事?
People started dying.
有人陆续死掉
And then their bodies-- It didn't make any sense.
接着他们的尸体... 一点道理都没有啊
They disappeared.
尸体消失了
Edward, I'd like to show something to you, if I may.
爱德华,可以的话我想给你看点东西
Do you recognize this man?
你还记得这个男的吗?
No.
不记得
That man, Edward, is Malcolm Rivers.
爱德华,那个男的叫马尔科姆里弗斯
He's had a very troubled life. He was arrested four years ago...
无恶不作,他在四年前遭到逮捕...
...and convicted of the murder of six people in a violent rampage.
被判凶残杀害了六人
-He did this. -Detective, please.
他干的 侦探,拜
Edward, listen to me.
爱德华,听我说
When faced with an intense trauma, a child's mind may fracture...
遭遇强烈精神创伤 孩童的心智可能产生分裂...
...creating disassociated identities.
...造成多重人格
That's exactly what happened to Malcolm Rivers.
马尔科姆里弗斯当时绝对是这种情形
He developed a condition that is commonly known...
他的情况发展成为众所周知的...
...as Multiple Personality Syndrome.
...多重人格症候群
Why are you telling me this?
你为何要告诉我这个?
Because you, Edward...
因为你,爱德华...
...are one of his personalities.
...是他的人格之一
What?
什么?
Jesus Christ! What the fuck did you do to my face?
天哪! 你们把我的脸怎么了?
-Keep calm. -Where is my face?
冷静点 我的脸在哪呢?
-That is your face. -Why am I tied up?
那是你的脸 干嘛把我绑起来?
-Keep calm. -Where is--?
冷静点 在哪呢...?
-Please. -Jesus Christ!
拜 天哪!
-Where is my face? -Stay calm.
我的脸呢? 保持冷静
No! I'm not gonna stay calm! Why am I tied up like this?
不! 我不要保持冷静! 干嘛把我这样绑起来?
Who are all these people? What happened at the motel?
这些人是谁? 汽车旅馆发生了什么事?
-Where is everybody? -They don't exist, Edward.
大伙儿人呢? 他们并不存在,爱德华
You were all created by Malcolm as a child.
你们都是马尔科姆小时候虚构出来的
-You're a liar! -Consider what you know.
你这骗子! 仔细想想你所知道的事情
-Everyone named after a state. -No.
每个人都以州名来命名 不
Everyone sharing the same birthday. Your blackouts.
每个人都同一天生日,你晕过去了
No! I was a cop!
不! 我是警察!
I was a cop in the Rampart Division of L.A.P.D. for six years.
我在洛城警局兰巴分部当了六年警察
Edward, please.
爱德华,拜
I live in Hollywood, in a studio apartment.
我住在好莱坞一栋制片厂公寓
-You don't live there. -I do live there!
你并没住在那里 我真的住在那里!
You don't live anywhere.
你不住任何地方
I know this is difficult to accept, but the face you saw in that mirror...
我知道这很难以接受 但你在镜中看到的脸
...is the face I've always seen when I talk to Edward or Paris or Larry...
就是当我和爱德华或巴黎或拉里讲话时 所看到的同一张脸
...or anyone else you've met tonight.
或者今晚你所碰到的任何人都是
Malcolm is in the midst of a medical treatment.
马尔科姆正处于药物治疗过程中
One which forces all his identities to confront one another for the first time.
起先强迫他所有的人格互相面对冲击
I knew there would be violence...
我知道会产生暴力...
...and with it, the number of the identities would be reduced.
随着暴力的产生,人格的数目会减少
Reduced?
减少?
One of the personalities you've met tonight, Edward...
爱德华,你今晚见到的这些人其中一个...
...committed those murders four years ago.
四年前犯下那些命案
He took control of Malcolm's body, as you have now...
他控制了你现在这个马尔科姆的肉体
...and released an unspeakable rage. And in 19 hours...
并释放出极度的愤怒 再过19个小时...
...Malcolm Rivers will be put to death because of those actions...
马尔科姆里弗斯将因那些行为被处死...
...unless I can convince that man...
除非我能说服那个人...
...that the killer is gone.
证明凶手不见了
I need you to stay with me. Edward?
我要你撑下去! 爱德华?
I need your help. I need your help to finish this.
我需要你的帮助 我需要你帮忙完成这件事
Edward, listen to me.
爱德华,听我说
Edward, stay with me.
爱德华,陪我
Listen to me. I need you to understand.
听我说,我需要你能了解
The killer cannot survive.
凶手是不容存活的
Edward!
爱德华!
Got it?
找到了吗?
I can't see a thing. Is there a flashlight?
什么也看不到,有没有手电筒?
Hang on. Hang on.
等等,等等
-You got a flashlight? -Yeah, yeah, it's dead. Goddamn it.
找到手电筒了? 有的,坏了,妈的
Shut up!
闭嘴!
Hey. What am I supposed to wear, man?
嘿,那我穿什么,老兄?
You're in it.
穿你这样就好了
Larry.
拉里
Larry, come here.
拉里,过来
Ed!
爱德华!
Larry!
拉里!
-Larry! -Paris.
巴黎
Larry?
拉里?
Larry? Larry?
拉里? 拉里?
Where are the keys to the truck?
卡车钥匙在哪?
-That was good, Larry. -We gotta get out of here.
很好,拉里 我们得离开这里
-Ed has the keys to the truck. -I got a spare right here.
爱德华有卡车的钥匙 我这里有备份钥匙
-Where is he? -I don't know. Here.
他在哪里? 不知道,接住
-What are you doing? -We need a gun.
你在干嘛? 我们需要一把枪
Holy shit!
真该死!
Give me the keys to the truck.
卡车钥匙给我
Ed!
爱德华!
We gotta get out of here!
我们得离开这里!
-Paris-- -He's coming. He's--
巴黎... 他来了,他...
-Stay here. -What's wrong with you?
待在这里 你怎么了?
Paris, listen to me.
巴黎,听我说
Stay here.
待在这里
It's gonna be okay.
会没事的
Throw me the keys to the truck, Ed.
卡车钥匙丢过来给我,爱德华
Throw me the keys to the truck. Stay there. Stay there!
卡车钥匙丢过来给我 站在那边,站住!
Ed! Ed! Ed!
爱德华! 爱德华! 爱德华!
Ed, let me see.
爱德华,让我瞧瞧伤势
We gotta get you to a hospital.
我们得送你到医院
We're gonna get you to a hospital, okay?
我们会送你到医院去好吗?
Stay with me because I'm gonna get you to the truck.
撑着点,因为我要扶你上卡车
Put your arm around my neck. You gotta hold on, okay?
手臂揽着我的脖子 你得撑下去,好吗?
You with me, Ed? Stay with me. Okay. One, two, three.
听的见我吗,爱德华? 撑下去 好的,一、二、三
You gotta help me get you up. Ed, you gotta push a little bit.
你得帮我让自己起来 爱德华,你得出点力气
Ed, why won't you let me help you?
爱德华,为何不让我帮你?
Where did you go before?
你之前去了哪里?
What did you see? Tell me what you saw.
你看到了什么? 告诉我你看见了什么
I saw you.
我看到你
I saw you in an orange grove.
我看到你在橘子林中
Why won't you let me help you?
为何不让我帮你?
Where did you go?
你去了哪里?
What did you see?
你看到了什么?
I saw you...
我看到你...
...in an orange grove.
...在橘子林中
The question, Your Honor, is whether to convict the body or the mind.
庭上,问题是不管生理上或心理上犯罪
His body committed these murders, that is true.
他的身体犯下这些命案却是千真万确的
The person who remains inside did not.
心理上却没有犯罪
Judge Taylor, that may not be true--
泰勒法官,那可能不是真的...
We witnessed the destruction of 10 identities tonight.
我们今晚见证到十种人格的摧毁
Nine were innocent and one was guilty.
九人无辜,一人有罪
They're not real!
他们不是真实的!
The violence that existed in him has been executed.
存在他身上的暴力已经处决了
Your Honor, Malcolm belongs in a state hospital.
庭上,马尔科姆属于州立医院
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada, it is the recommendation of this court...
关于内华达州里弗斯一案,本庭建议...
...that Mr. Rivers' execution be stayed.
里弗斯先生予以缓刑
I am transferring Mr. Rivers to state psychiatric services...
我要将里弗斯先生转到州立精神院中心
...under the care of Dr. Mallick.
接受马里克医生的治疗
Cracked heels and washed-out horns Blow into my face with scorn
磨破脚跟、声嘶力竭,却换来轻蔑的嘲弄
But it's not that way I wasn't born to lose you
但不是那样,我不是生来要失去你
I want you
我要你
I want you so bad
我非常想要你
Timmy.
提米
No, please don't.
不,拜不要
No, Timmy, please.
不,提米,求求你
What is it, Malcolm?
怎么了,马尔科姆?
Malcolm?
马尔科姆?
Whores don't get a second chance.
妓女没有第二次机会
When I was going up the stairs
当我上楼时
I met a man who wasn't there
碰见一个原本不在那里的男人
He wasn't there again today
今天他还是不在那里
I wish I wish he'd go away
我希望...我希望他离开了